# LEO AQUIBA SENDEROVSKY

#### Sr. Video Editor - Post Production Coordinator

Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1406 · (+5411) 3045-2585

<u>l.a.senderovsky@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/lsender · behance.net/leosenderovsky</u>

I've been working in the audiovisual industry for over 15 years, as a video editor, post production coordinator, script consultant and film professor. Over the course of my work experience, I have combined an initial passion for audiovisual storytelling and teaching, and a growing passion for web design and development. Currently, I'm in search of new professional challenges and I want to achieve new goals in both audiovisual and IT fields.

### SOFTWARE SKILLS

Adobe Suite (Premiere, After Effects, Photoshop, Illustrator), AVID Media Composer, Final Cut Pro, Da Vinci Resolve.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

INFOBAE, Buenos Aires · Visual Storyteller / Sr. Video Editor -

02/2022 - Present

Infobae is the most read Spanish news site in the world. As a member of Infobae Audiovisual (Medialab) Staff, I'm in charge of editing all kind of videos for its website and its social media channels (breaking news videos, interviews, etc), as well as promo videos for the company's clients. I've also edited several documentaries for the website, such as Malvinas: a 40 años de la guerra, Malvinas, el final, 10 años del Papa Francisco, Un año de invasión rusa en Ucrania, La caída de Isabel Perón and Alfonsín y el rezo laico que unió al país.

LN+ / FRAME, Buenos Aires · Sr. Video Editor / Staff Coordinator

09/2016 - 02/2022

Member of Frame's Editing Staff Department at LN+ TV channel, since the beginning of its operation. From June 2019 until my resignation, I was both an editor and Frame's editing chief staff coordinator, responsible for editors' replacements and inductions, and the remote post production workflow during Covid quarantine in 2020.

As an editor, I was in charge of tv programs such as <u>"La gran batalla" (2017)</u>, <u>"Perdidos en Buenos Aires" (2017)</u> or "Hablemos de otra cosa" (2018-2022).

#### CACTUS CINE - EGOLAND - LEMOS FILMS, Buenos Aires · Video Editor

2017 - 2023

Freelance video editor of corporate videos for companies like FV, <u>Sura</u> or <u>Celsur</u>, and social media promo videos, such as <u>ABB FIA Formula E in Mexico City 2022</u>.

#### **GEEK LOUNGE**, Buenos Aires · Video Editor

11/2021-12/2021

Freelance video editor for "Twitch Creators Highlights" promos for Twitch LATAM.

#### NBA LATAM, Buenos Aires · Video Editor

06/2019-03/2021

Editor for <u>Semana NBA</u>, weekly social web program, and other NBA Latam social media channels videos. Editing of all the <u>NBA G League International Challenge Uruguay 2019</u> campaign event videos.

#### KINO BOVIO, Buenos Aires · Video Editor

09/2016 - 09/2016

Editor of social media videos for the Government of Buenos Aires Province, Ministry of Transport, Ministry of Education, McDonald's, among other company clients.

#### FILM&CO / CACTUS CINE, Buenos Aires · Video Editor - Post Production Coordinator

11/2013 - 08/2016

Scriptwriter, editor and post production coordinator at Film&Co, a Cactus Cine department for corporate and institutional videos, with clients like FV, Ferrum, Eidico, RSA, Sura Seguros, Universidad Kennedy. Examples: <a href="mailto:Answer Seguros Youtube Spot">Answer Seguros Youtube Spot</a> (editor), <a href="mailto:Eidico Casas web spot">Eidico Casas web spot</a> (writer and editor), <a href="mailto:Eidico web spot">Eidico web spot</a> (writer and editor).

Editor of <u>"Somos futboleros" TV program</u> (DeporTV), "Conversaciones en La Nación" and "Protagonistas" (Cactus Cine - La Nación)

#### ESTUDIO MW, Buenos Aires · Video Editor

04/2012 - 11/2013

Editor of social event videos and live video edition at social events.

### SKANSKA / DINÁMICA COMUNICACIONES, Buenos Aires · Video Editor

09/2011 - 12/2012

Freelance video editor for corporate clients.

**DIGIKOL**, Buenos Aires · Head of Multimedia Department

10/2008 - 11/2011

Video production and multimedia services for company clients and company own websites. Project manager of company websites.

# **EDUCATION**

Film Director / Film Professor · Universidad del Cine, Buenos Aires (2008)

### **OTHER COURSES:**

Motion Graphics · Coderhouse, Buenos Aires (2022)

**Web Development / Javascript** · Coderhouse, Buenos Aires (2021)

Script Doctor · El Laboratorio de Guión, Buenos Aires (2010)